原创翻译  双语字幕
《超女》前情提要
Previously on Supergirl...
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
创伤后心理医生的转诊文件
Referrals for post-trauma psychologists.
翻译     DustD  洗七里  DerbyNinja
凯莉  我说了我没事
Kelly, I said I'm fine.
你先穿上这个
Put this on first.
你看起来跟她一模一样
You really look exactly like her.
翻译     阿p  左左  C·A
我的美国同胞们
My fellow Americans,
我们伟大国家的核心遭受了袭击
the heart of our great nation was attacked...
校对     肉松  饿得慌
超女  你现在是头号公敌
Supergirl, you are now public enemy number one.
我们知道不是你做的
We know you didn't do this.
时间轴    想念Gallifrey的Wholock  三水
我们会查明真相
We're gonna find out the truth.
齐心协力
Together.
贝克总统公告
我的美国同胞们
My fellow Americans,
后期     你是不是饿得慌
自从超女袭击白宫已经过了一天
it has been a day since Supergirl's attack on the White House.
这明显是对
In apparent retaliation
总监     你是不是饿得慌
我们废除《外星人赦免法》的报复
for our repeal of the Alien Amnesty Act.
目前她与同谋们目前依然在逃
While she and those with whom she conspired remain at large,
我有义务
I have an obligation
保障所有公民的安全
to ensure the safety of all citizens.
所以  在今天19点整
So, at 1900 hours today,
我将执行日落到日出戒严
I am imposing a sundown to sunup curfew.
他们最好抓住她
They better catch her.
这不是超女做的
Supergirl did not do this.
在街头滞留的人类将被收押
Humans caught loitering will be cited.
外星人将被尽一切手段阻止
Aliens will be stopped by any means necessary.
还有超女  请来自首
And to Supergirl, turn yourself in.
我们不想与你进行战争
We do not want a war with you
但我们发誓将运用我们的一切手段
but we vow to use every asset in our power
来伸张正义
to see that justice is done.
正义  真是个骗子
Justice? What a crock!
救命  谁来救救我  我被困住了
Help! Somebody help! I'm trapped.
有人遇到麻烦了
Someone's in trouble.
我得走了
I have to go.
你听到总统说的了  外边不安全
You heard the president, it isn't safe.
如果政府想要阻止我帮助别人
If the government wants to stop me from helping people,
那就让他们试试
let them try.
来
Here.
这是私人拘捕
This is a citizen's arrest.
这个人需要帮助  放下枪
This man needs help. Put the gun--
住手  你们在新闻上看到的那个人不是我
Stop! What you saw in the news, that wasn't me.
我们看到录像了
We saw the footage.
你退后  叛徒
You stay back, traitor.
我不会伤害任...
I'm not going to hurt any--
你会误杀别人的
You're gonna kill someone.
她会杀了我们的
She's gonna kill us.
我可以先杀了她
Not if I kill her first.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
谢谢你
Thank you.
但我不明白
But I don't get it.
你救了我  但是却袭击了白宫
You saved my life but you attacked the White House?
我的女儿看到了
My daughter saw that.
你曾是她的英雄  但你...
You were her hero and you...
你伤了她的心
You crushed her.
超 女
第四季 第十八集
居然有人相信
I mean, people actually believe
我袭击了白宫
that I attacked the White House.
他们认为我是恐怖分子
They think I'm a terrorist.
我帮了别人那么多年  一句谎言就抹杀了这一切
Years of helping people just wiped away with one lie.
不是一句谎言  而是许多谎言
No, not one lie, it's lots of lies.
本·洛克伍德说好几个月的谎言了
And Ben Lockwood has been telling whoppers for months.
他在制造分裂
He's just creating division.
大部分国民很害怕
And then most of the country is just terrified
现在他们正在试图理解这一切
and now they're looking for solutions to make any sense of it.
难道真相不是更重要吗
Shouldn't the truth matter more?
莱克斯参与其中就不同了
Not when Lex is involved.
他是欺骗的高手  完美的迷魂烟
He's an expert at perception. Consummate gaslighter.
他可以让你怀疑你所认定的真相
He can make you doubt things that you know are true.
我坚信
Listen, I really believe that
我们三个人一起合作
the three of us working together
才是还你清白并抓住他的最好机会
is our best chance of vindicating you and catching him.
那他是怎么做到的
Okay, so how did he do it?
我们知道那不是异超女  我调查过了
We know it wasn't Bizarro, I already checked.
变形者  全息投影  形象诱发器
Shapeshifter, hologram? Image inducer...
不可能  热信号不匹配
No, that can't be right. The heat signatures don't match.
我不明白
I don't understand.
他到底想干什么
What is he up to?
我不知道  但我们会找到真相的
I don't know. But we will find the truth
然后我们会扳倒他
and we will bring him down.
我有条线索能帮我们做到这一点
All right, and to that end I've got a lead.
但是从我妈那里听来的
But it comes from my mother.
她说莱克斯从
She said that Lex's escape
斯特赖克岛监狱逃走不是第一次了
from Stryker's Island prison wasn't his first.
他几个月来一直自由进出
That he's been coming and going as he pleases for months.
所以有人在帮助他
So someone's been helping him.
典狱长
The warden.
Warden!
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to interrupt.
超女
Supergirl.
我想你和卢瑟女士来这里
I assume you're here with Ms. Luthor
是要自首
to turn yourself in.
你可能需要重新考虑一下
You might want to rethink that.
贿赂和逃税是重罪
Bribery and tax evasion are felonies.
帮助莱克斯·卢瑟这样的罪犯也是
So is helping a criminal like Lex Luthor.
他在哪里
Where is he?
别胡扯了
Don't be ridiculous.
开曼群岛账户832591290
Account number 832591290 in the Cayman Islands.
好吧
Okay.
我可能收了些钱
I may have taken some money.
但我不知道他在哪
But I don't know where he is.
你让他自由进出
You let him come and go.
他从没告诉过我他会去哪里
He never told me where he went.
你就没想过问一下吗
You never thought to ask?
我不过是睁一只眼闭一只眼而已
All I did was turn a blind eye
毕竟他威胁要杀了我
and that was after he threatened to kill me.
得了吧  那是他的一贯伎俩
Oh, please, he does that to everyone.
但这里什么都没有  联调局已经调查了牢房
But there's nothing here. The FBI already checked his cell.
他们也调查了你
They also checked you.
所以或许他们漏掉了什么
So maybe they missed something else.
你指望我带着美国头号通缉犯通过狱警吗
You expect me to march America's most wanted past my guards?
国防部会立马赶来
The DOD will be all over us in no time.
到时你可以引开他们
Well, then you can give them a distraction.
与此同时我们搜索莱克斯的牢房
And while we search Lex's cell
你还有时间可以在你俩被逮捕前
you'll have time to call your husband
给你丈夫打电话
before you're both arrested.
我的丈夫与此无关
My husband had nothing to do with this.
-他对账户的事一无所知  -好吧
- He doesn't know anything about the account. - Fine.
那么你让我们进入莱克斯的牢房
So you give us access to Lex's cell,
我们就在联络当局的时候
and we'll leave your husband out of it
不提及你的丈夫
when we contact the authorities.
我可以把D区狱警调开两个小时
I could clear the guards out of D block for two hours.
莱克斯的牢房就在那扇门后
Lex's cell is through that door.
你在特区放的烟花真漂亮  超女
Nice fireworks in DC, Supergirl.
那不是我干的
That wasn't me.
这里是关罪犯  不是关恐怖分子的地方
This place is for criminals not terrorists.
好了  继续走  强势一点
Okay, keep walking. Stay strong.
欢迎来到斯特赖克  超女
Welcome to Stryker's, Supergirl.
超女
Supergirl.
超女  超女
Supergirl. Supergirl.
这是《汉尼拔翻越阿尔卑斯山》
It's Hannibal Crossing the Alps.
真是自命不凡
So pretentious.
看到莱克斯的东西  我会觉得很焦虑
It's so unnerving being around all Lex's stuff.
让我又回忆起了自己悲惨的童年
Brings back memories of my miserable childhood.
甚至还有一模一样的棋盘
Even has the same chess board.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我知道这听起来很傻  但我们小时候
I know it sounds silly but when we were little,
我和莱克斯会在棋子里给对方留字条
Lex and I used to leave notes for each other inside chess pieces.
找到了
Here it is.
死亡时间凌晨4点3分
Time of death 4:03 a.m.
这是什么
What is it?
没什么  只是莱克斯想扰乱我的思绪
Nothing, it's just Lex trying to mess with my head.
那后面的数字呢
And the number on the back?
-7  16  18  是个日期吗  -对  这是...
- 7/16/18. A date? - Yes, it's...
1918年7月16日
July 16, 1918.
是罗曼诺夫在俄罗斯被处决的日子
It's the date that Romanovs were executed in Russia.
莱克斯曾经叫我"迷失的公主"
Lex used to call me the Lost Princess.
就像安娜斯塔西娅一样
Just like Anastasia.
这是个将死的棋阵
It's a checkmate pattern.
安娜斯塔西娅就是我
Anastasia's me.
莱克斯的日记
Lex's diaries.
他为什么要把日记留下
Why would he leave them?
因为他知道我会来找他
Because he knew I'd come looking for him.
他喜欢折磨我
And he loves to torment me.
他知道我最不想做的事
He knew the last thing I'd wanna do
就是在他的记忆中畅游
would be to go swimming in his memories.
他心理变态扭曲  但至少他始终如一
He's sick, and he's twisted but at least he's consistent.
洛克伍德
Lockwood.
我现在可是
Secretary Lockwood now
内阁级外星事务部的洛克伍德秘书
of the cabinet-level Department of Alien Affairs.
应该是纳欣诺市监狱的42053号囚犯
Should be inmate 42053 of the National City prison.
很高兴见到你
So good to see you, too.
秘书先生  我们能为您做些什么
Mr. Secretary, how can we help you?
我来这里是为了征用
I am here to requisition any alien technology
可以牵制超女的外星技术或武器
or weapons that may assist in containing Supergirl.
然后你们要召唤超女
And then you'll summon Supergirl
来这里
here.
好让你伏击她吗
So you can ambush her?
好让我们伸张正义
So we can serve justice.
即使我们可以召唤超女
Even if we could summon Supergirl,
我也要拿到总统令  才能满足你的要求
I would need a presidential order to comply with your request,
这是超查部章程第4段A小节的规定
as per paragraph four subsection A of the DEO charter.
对吗  上校
Isn't that correct, Colonel?
这是我们的规程
That is the protocol.
之后我们会很乐意配合
Then we'd be happy to comply.
好吧  我问你个问题
Okay, let me ask you a question.
你确定想浪费我的时间吗
Are you absolutely certain that you want to waste my time?
我们可能不太了解对方  洛克伍德先生
We may not know each other well, Mr. Lockwood,
但我是按部就班做事的  即使是面对秘书
but I do things by the book, even for secretaries.
A小组  现在去军械库
Alpha team, to the armory now.
上校  你为什么要让步
Colonel, why are you capitulating?
我们刚才已经把他逼退了
We just got him to back off.
如果是总统派他来的
If the president sent him,
他很快就会拿到总统令
he'll be back with the order in no time.
我们都知道超女是无辜的
We both know that Supergirl is innocent.
我们要做的不是去质疑  局长
It's not our job to question, Director,
所以我需要你交出超女给你的
which is why I need you to hand over the signal watch
信号手表
Supergirl gave you.
如果我们有办法召唤超女
If we are in possession of a way to summon Supergirl,
就必须试试
we have to use it.
命令就是命令
Orders are orders.
按两次  她就会收到警报
Press it twice, she gets the alert.
你好
Hello.
我马上就到
I'll be right there.
你叫哈雷上校按两次信号手表
You told Colonel Haley to press the signal watch twice.
对  你知道代号
Yes. You know the code.
按一次她会过来  按两次
Push it once she comes, push it twice,
说明这是个陷阱  别来
it's a trap, don't come.
这样她就安全了
Thus keeping her safe.
聪明
Brilliant.
但是超女并不是唯一有风险的人
Yet Supergirl isn't the only one at risk.
既然本杰明·洛克伍德今天冲着她来了
Since Benjamin Lockwood has come for her today,
那么很有可能
there is a high probability
下个星期他会冲着所有的外星人来
that next week he'll come for the entire alien registry.
-是的  -在那之后
- Yeah. - After which
他将开始围捕所有外星人
he'll start rounding up aliens without discrimination,
因此  我建议
ergo I propose
我们从数据库中清除外星人的注册信息
we scrub the alien registry from our database.
如果你这么想的话
If that's what you think,
在我能让哈雷信服道理之前
and until I can get Haley to listen to reason,
我们要尽我们所能
then we need to do whatever we can.
但是拜托  多克斯特工
But please, Agent Dox,
要保密
be clandestine.
当然
Of course.
如你所知  没有人比我更会保密了
As you well know, no one is more clandestine than I.
没有人
No one.
紧张吗
Nervous?
不紧张
Not at all.
我今天已经在脑海里取消过三次预约了
I've just canceled three times in my head already today,
就是这样
so there's that.
帕克医生是全国最好的创伤治疗专家
Doctor Park is the best trauma therapist in National City.
她对创伤后应激障碍了若指掌
She practically wrote the book on PTSD.
我知道这很难
Still it's hard, I know.
我见过有的士兵
I have seen soldiers
因为要接受接下来的治疗而吓得动弹不了
paralyzed over what you're about to do.
我为你感到骄傲
I am so proud of you.
老爸也会的
And Dad would be, too.
谢谢
Thank you.
艾丽克斯  你好
Alex, hi.
当然
Of course.
到时候见
I'll see you then.
谢谢你能见到我
Thank you for meeting me.
别客气
Any time.
怎么了
So what's up?
我想得到你身为治疗师的建议
I wanted to get your advice on something, being a therapist.
抱歉  但愿这样不会太冒昧
I'm sorry, I hope that's not weird that I asked.
我可以为朋友破一次例
I can make a one-time exception for a friend.
好的
Okay.
我和我的指挥官
My commanding officer and I
都认为外星事务部
both agree that we think that something suspicious
发生的事情有猫腻
is going on at the Department of Alien Affairs,
我想告诉她
and I am trying to tell her
我们不能盲目地服从他们所有的命令
that we can't just follow their every order
但她却坚持要遵循指挥系统
but she insists on the chain of command.
我不知道怎么才能说通她
And I don't know how to reach her.
我可以试试吗
Well, can I take a stab?
拜托
Please.
你要收起怒气
You need to stop getting angry
变得聪明起来
and get smart.
我以前的指挥官很混蛋
Okay, now, I had a real jerk of a CO.
我们驻扎在巴什尔郊区的
We were stationed at a checkpoint
一个检查站
on the outskirts of Bashur.
有一天  有个男人开着破旧的皮卡
And one day, a man pulled up
停了过来
in this decrepit pickup,
他怀孕的妻子坐在后面
his pregnant wife in the back,
他只是想找那个地方唯一的助产士
and he's just trying to get to the only midwife in the region.
只要穿过小镇800多米就能到
Just half a mile across town.
指挥官不在乎
And the CO doesn't care.
规矩就是规矩  他没有拿到批准文件
Rules are rules and he doesn't have the right papers.
那你当时怎么做的
So what did you do?
我大声嘶喊说要做正确的事
I yelled and screamed about doing the right thing
结果徒劳无功
and got nowhere.
但是我的军士说服了指挥官
But my sergeant convinced the CO
不让那个人的妻子和孩子冒生命危险
that it would be safer for his unit
对他的部队来说会更安全
not to risk the life of the man's wife and child.
他知道指挥官最在乎的是什么
He knew what the CO cared most about.
他的手下
His men.
你无法改变他人
You can't change people.
但你可以唤醒他们的良知
But you can appeal to who they are.
即使最强硬的指挥官都有在乎的人
Even the toughest COs care about something.
我猜猜  现在你希望你没打过电话给我
Let me guess, right now you're wishing that you never called me.
其实正好相反
Actually, it's quite the opposite.
我真的很高兴你没走
I'm really glad you didn't leave.
存有外星人注册表的根服务器
The root server containing the alien registry
就在地下五层的地下室里
is located in a vault on sub-level five.
授权人员必须通过一系列安检
Authorized personnel have to pass through a series of security checks.
第一  声纹识别
First, a voiceprint identification.
谢天谢地哈雷上校很爱说话
Thankfully Colonel Haley is good at talking,
而我很擅长录音
and I am good at recording.
哈雷上校
Colonel Haley.
第二  视网膜扫描
Next, a retinal scan.
我可以用我的形象诱发器
I can scramble the pattern of the retina
打乱视网膜模式  混淆网关计算机
in my image inducer to confuse the gateway computer.
接下来就是最具挑战的一步
Then the most challenging step.
有警卫看守的电梯
The guarded elevator.
通过研究伊森·亨特  《碟中谍》里的高手
From studying Ethan Hunt, master of the impossible mission,
《碟中谍》系列的主角
显然绕过警卫的答案是找托词
the obvious answer to bypass the guards would be subterfuge.
是的  哈雷上校
Yes, Colonel Haley,
我正赶往那里
I'm hurrying there as we speak.
哈雷上校  她没太有耐心
Colonel Haley, she's very impatient.
需要拿些东西  地下五层
Need something. Sub-level five.
全国外星人注册表
进入数据库
删除注册表
全国外星人注册表
进入数据库
删除注册表
确认  取消
如果有人发现了我的行为怎么办
What if my actions are discovered?
对外星人实施惩罚的报复手段
And the powers that be retaliate
就会变得更加严厉
by coming down even harder on the aliens.
但话说回来  如果我不删除
Then again, if I don't delete it,
外星事务部就会立即将我朋友驱逐出境
Alien Affairs will immediately target my friends for deportation.
如果我真的删除了
And if I do delete it,
那要怎样阻止政府
well, then what's to stop the government
想出别的办法来向他们下手呢
from finding a new way to target them?
难以抉择
Ah, spruck!
我接下来要做的事
There is a perfect 50/50 chance
有一半几率
that what I am about to do
是绝对错的
is absolutely wrong.
这样看来
Well...
如果没有精确的解答方案
If there is no mathematical solution
那也许我应该找一个
then perhaps I should find a more...
更具创造性的办法
creative one.
这些只是每月的开销
These are just monthly expenses.
支付给一半的预警和所有的囚犯
Payoffs to half the guards and all of the inmates.
这一本里全都是超人以及他被假定的失败
This one's all about Superman and his supposed failings.
真是让人火大
It's infuriating.
怎么了
What is it?
这是我小时候的事
It's from my childhood.
从四岁起
It's an inventory of
我所犯的过失和错误
all the faults and mistakes I've made since I was four.
他就是这个德行
This is how he operates.
我情绪激动  他就赢了
I get flooded with emotion and he wins.
我觉得我做不到
I don't think I can do this.
对面有个宅男偷窥狂
We have a peeping Tom across the way.
你觉得他会知道些什么吗
You think he knows anything?
我知道我应该心存感激
I get that I should be grateful.
我的确很感激
And I am.
但是呢
But?
但是我不爽
But I'm pissed.
我知道我必须来这里
I know I need to be here
但这让人觉得...
but this just feels...
我是守护者
I'm Guardian
我保护人们
and I protect people.
人们尊敬我
And people look up to me when...
你觉得你不值得别人来帮你吗
Do you feel like you don't deserve help?
我觉得我不该需要别人帮忙
I feel like I shouldn't need help.
我觉得我应该足够坚强来克服这一切
I feel like I should be strong enough to just get over this.
当然如果你有治愈仙丹  我愿意吃
Of course if you have a magic pill I'll take it.
可惜  这个过程需要时间
Sadly, this process takes time.
今天  我可以给你一个着手点  帮你对抗焦虑
For today, I can give you a starting point to deal with anxiety
或者任何有可能出现的负面情绪
or any negative feelings that may come up.
一种平复情绪的方法
A calming tool.
当然
Okay, sure.
叫做双侧刺激
It's called bilateral stimulation.
如果你开始出现症状  它可以帮助你恢复
So if you start experiencing symptoms, it can help pull you back.
手臂交叉  手指勾在一起
Cross your arms and interlock your fingers.
吸气
Breathe in.
吐气
Breathe out.
轻拍
Tap.
如果你觉得舒服的话
Now, if you're comfortable,
想一个你觉得安全的地方
think of a place where you feel safe.
使用这个方法  詹姆斯
Use the tool, James.
双臂交叉
Cross your arms,
手指勾在一起  吸气
interlock your fingers, breathe in.
轻拍
Tap.
这是治疗的一部分
This is part of the process.
需要耐心
It takes patience
但是会起效的
but it does work.
我知道会的
I know it will.
你好啊
Hey, there.
恶名昭彰的莱克斯·卢瑟的邻居
Neighbor to the infamous Lex Luthor, huh?
是的  真是无上的荣幸
Oh, yeah, it was a true privilege.
你这里的视野不错嘛
I mean, you have a great view.
这几周有看到什么可疑的事吗
See anything suspicious the last few weeks?
莱克斯所做的每一件都很可疑
Everything Lex did was suspicious.
让我猜猜  你希望我向他的宿敌
And let me guess, now you want me to rat him out
出卖他吗
to his archnemesis?
想想那感觉有多好
Think of how good that will feel.
终于能将他绳之以法
To help finally bring him to justice.
你指望我相信你吗
You expect me to trust you?
你就是个叛徒
You are literally a traitor.
但是你又在乎什么呢
But what do you care, right?
大摇大摆地走进来  陷害我们
Waltzing in here and putting a target on all our backs.
-你说什么  -整个国家都很想铲除你
- Excuse me? - The entire country is itching to nuke you.
当他们铲除你的时候
And when they do,
猜猜还有谁会被铲除
guess who else gets nuked?
不  他们不会这么做的
No, they wouldn't do that.
他们想这么做
They want to.
没人在乎无名小卒
Nobody cares about the little people.
即使我们为正义而战
Even if we're fighting for justice by say,
比如说公开有关非法无人机战争的机密文件
releasing classified documents about illegal drone warfare.
等等  你是斯蒂夫·罗麦利
Wait. You're Steve Lomeli.
是你从国防部窃取了数据
You stole all that data from the DOD.
我只是揭露了真相
I exposed the truth.
也为此失去了自由
And I paid for it with my freedom.
因为  我不像你
Because, unlike you,
并不能凌驾于法律之上
I'm not above the law.
真是荒谬  我...
That's ridiculous. I...
是吗  你有多少次
Oh, really? How many times has your
用一意孤行的粗暴方式
unilateral bull-in-a-china-shop approach
毁掉了至关重要的证据
destroyed exculpatory evidence?
有个词可以形容你们这样的人
The term for someone like you
有害的自恋者
is malignant narcissist.
我是在帮助别人
I help people.
少来吧  根本不是
Oh, no, you don't.
你染指的东西都会被毁掉
Everything you touch, you ruin.
尼娅·纳尔  我理解你现在可能不太想见我
Nia Nal, I understand this interaction might be difficult for you
毕竟从我们上次在医院
given that we haven't spoken since our incredible
浪漫而惊险的见面后  就再没说过话了
yet devastating romantic encounter at the hospital.
是啊  我一直吃不下东西
Yeah, I've barely been able to eat.
是啊  我最近也遇到了一个难题
Yes, well, I too have been caught in quite a conundrum.
本·洛克伍德想给超女下套
Ben Lockwood is trying to trap Supergirl.
他的下一步计划就是拿到外星人注册记录
His next step will be obtaining the alien registry.
我们可以现在删除
We could delete it right now,
扼杀这个可能性
avoid that possibility,
但是这样做有后果
but that could backfire
可能会让政府陷入水深火热之中
and bring the government down twice as hard.
两种可能性平分秋色
The odds are a perfect 50/50.
你的直觉是什么
What does your gut tell you?
我的直觉是做决定应该根据事实
That decisions should be made based on facts
而不是主观感觉
and not intestinal inclinations.
请告诉我
Now, please tell me,
我该怎么办
what do I do?
如果你想问我的意见...
If you want my opinion--
不  我不要意见
No, I do not,
我希望你直接告诉我怎么做
I want you to literally tell me what I do.
你梦一下注册资料的未来
Dream the future of the registry.
还存在吗  或者不存在
Does it exist? Does it not?
你告诉我这个结果  我就知道我干了什么
If you tell me that, then you tell me what I did
然后我就可以去做了
so that I could do it.
我想知道我的后代是否有超能力
So when I want to know about my descendant's superpowers
你就说"你会毁掉时空的结构"
it's all "You'll destroy the fabric of space and time."
可你想知道将来如何的时候...
But when you want to know the future it's--
没有其他办法了
There is no other way.
好吧
Fine.
你没有毁掉注册资料
You don't destroy the registry.
真是荒谬
That's ridiculous.
我当然得毁掉
Of course I have to destroy it.
这不就得了
Exactly.
-什么  -答案出来了
- What? - That's the answer.
你得毁掉注册资料
You have to destroy the registry.
但你梦到的结果是相反的
But you just dreamt the opposite.
我什么都没梦
I didn't dream anything.
有时候听到错误答案
Sometimes hearing the wrong answer
才能意识到正确答案是什么
shows you what the right one is.
主观感觉
Intestinal inclination.
也不赖吧
Not so bad, is it?
谢谢你  金女士
Well, thank you, Ms. Kim.
非常感激
I appreciate it.
怎么了  丹弗斯局长
What is it, Director Danvers?
上校
Colonel.
你一辈子都在当兵
You've spent your life in service.
你做的每件事都是为了祖国
Everything you do is for the good of our country.
你认为这是你的道德标准
You see that as a moral imperative.
但是有些命令并不道德
But some orders are immoral.
听从这些命令并不代表你是一名好兵
And following them does not make you a good soldier,
这代表着你是共犯
it makes you complicit.
够了  丹弗斯局长
That is enough, Director Danvers.
本·洛克伍德想要伏击超女
Ben Lockwood wants to ambush Supergirl.
他想处决她
He wants to execute her.
但我们都知道  那些指控是虚假的
While you and I both know that she's been falsely accused.
我知道违反命令有风险
Look, I know that it's risky to defy orders
但是如今的局面  你要考虑的不仅是自己
but you have much more to consider than just yourself here.
你的女儿呢
What about your daughter?
你别把我女儿扯进来
You leave my daughter out of this.
我来这里好几个月
In all my months here I've revealed to you
只给了你一项个人信息
exactly one piece of personal information.
就一项
One piece--
你现在就要拿这一项来要挟我吗
And now you wanna use that as leverage against me?
-上校  -更不必说
- Colonel-- - Not to mention lying
信号手表的事你撒了谎
about the signal watch.
我知道的比你想象的多  按一下她就会来
Yes, I know more than you think. One click, she comes.
按两下她就不来
Two clicks, she stays away.
你在透支自己的运气  丹弗斯
You're pushing your luck here, Danvers,
总有一天  你的运气会用完
and one day you're going to push it too far.
出去吧
Dismissed.
监狱长
Hey, there, Warden.
监狱长是你的名还是姓呢
Is Warden your first name or your last?
你怎么来了
What are you doing here?
收到了警报提示
Got an alert.
老板的牢房里来了氪星人
Kryptonian in the boss' cell.
曾经仰慕我的人
Well, people who used to admire me
现在觉得我是美国的叛徒
now think I am an American traitor.
而讨厌我的人
And the people that hate me
正在庆祝我的垮台
are reveling in my downfall.
你没有垮台  超女  不过是个小挫折
Okay, this is not your downfall, Supergirl, it's a glitch.
不是你干的
You didn't do it.
我们都知道幕后黑手是莱克斯
We both know Lex is behind this,
很快大家都会知道的
and soon everyone else will, too.
我比任何人都理解
Okay, I know better than anyone what it's like
因为莫须有的罪名被指控的感觉
to be falsely accused of a crime you didn't commit, okay?
不好受
It's not fun.
确实如此
No, it's not.
但是翻看杀人犯哥哥的日记
But neither is reading through your murderous brother's journals
重温那些可怕的记忆也不好受
and reliving traumatic memories.
光看着莱克斯的笔记
Just looking at Lex's handwriting
就像眼睛被针扎一样
is like needles in my eyes.
也许这一切都是徒劳
Maybe this is a wild-goose chase.
也许根本没有线索链
Maybe there's no clue trail,
这只是莱克斯一如既往地在折磨我
just Lex torturing me like he always does.
我们离开这里吧
Let's just get out of here.
不  莉娜  等等
No. No, Lena, wait.
你我这样的人  永不言弃
People like you and me, we don't give up.
我们一定能查出线索
So we will find something
也一定能阻止他
and we're going to stop him.
早上好  D区的各位朋友
Good morning, Cell Block D.
-这是...  -奥蒂斯·格雷夫斯
- Is that-- - Otis Graves.
我正在莱克斯电台实时直播
Coming to you live from WLEX.
我们将抽取一名幸运来电者送出礼物
We have a giveaway for one lucky caller.
第一名逮捕超女的人
First person to apprehend Supergirl
这辈子再也不用在监狱里
gets a lifetime of not being in prison anymore.
祝大家好运  牢房即将打开
Good luck. Lines are opening now.
再过30秒就要开始暴乱了
We've got about 30 seconds before there's a riot.
-我去找奥蒂斯  -我跟你一起去
- I'm gonna find Otis. - Wait, I'm coming with you.
不行  整个区的牢房
No, no, the whole cell
都已经被打开  太危险了
block was just set free, it's too dangerous.
但要想找到莱克斯  那个笨蛋是最大的机会
But that numskull's our best hope of finding Lex.
所以我会去
Which is why I will go.
你必须查出莱克斯隐藏了什么
You need to find out what Lex is hiding.
我要把外面的门焊上
I'm gonna weld that outside door
防止奥蒂斯进来
so Otis can't get in.
我再说一句  这是氪石防护盾
Before you go... It's a Kryptonite shield.
如果莱克斯真把奥蒂斯变成金属人带回来
If Lex did bring Otis back as Metallo,
你会需要它
you're gonna need it.
谢谢
Thanks.
-祝你好运  -你也是
- Good luck. - You too.
国家颁布戒严令的第二天
As the nation enters the second day of martial law,
全国范围内出现了食物短缺
food shortages and an uptick in violent crime
暴力犯罪激增
has been reported across the country.
L公司总裁莉娜·卢瑟的哥哥莱克斯·卢瑟
Adding to this tension is the escape of Lex Luthor,
他的逃脱恶化了局势
brother of L-Corp CEO, Lena Luthor.
典狱长 我们时间不多了
Warden, we don't have much time.
我需要你帮我找到...
I need you to help me find a--
一个疯子
psychopath.
你个混蛋
You bastard.
"爸爸又情绪失控了"
"Father lost his temper again..."
莉娜
Lena.
给我回来
Get back here now!
"莉娜把他最宝贝的钢笔送给了我"
"Lena stole his prized fountain pen for me.
"约旦国王送给他的那一支"
"The one presented to him by the King of Jordan."
"莉娜渴望我的关注"
"Lena craves my attention."
"真可怜"
"Pathetic."
"她要是知道自己有多优秀  就不必这样了"
"If she knew how brilliant she was, she wouldn't need it."
要是他找到我们怎么办
What if he finds us?
别担心  他喝醉的时候爬不上来
Don't worry, he can't climb when he's drunk.
等我长大
When I grow up,
我会成为世界上最有钱的人
I'm gonna have all the money in the world.
我要建一个房子
And I'm gonna build a house
让我们俩永远都不受伤害
and I'm gonna keep us safe forever.
就建在这里
I'll build it right there.
那不是阿尔卑斯山
Those aren't the Alps.
你在玩什么把戏  哥哥
What are you playing at, brother?
奥蒂斯·格雷夫斯在哪儿
Where's Otis Graves?
巧了巧了
Well, well, well.
这不是李·哈维·超女吗
If it isn't Lee Harvey Supergirl.
李·哈维 被认为是肯尼迪遇刺案的主凶
看来变绿还挺容易的
Turns out it's easy being green.
不止你一个人有姓卢瑟的朋友
You're not the only one who's friends with a Luthor.
我这儿的心脏有三倍大
My heart's grown three sizes in here.
总统下令  所有人听好
President's orders, boys.
如果超女在里面  就别让她出来
If Supergirl's in there, she is not coming out.
这监狱的名字不是白叫的
They don't call it the slammer for nothing.
超女
Supergirl!
奥蒂斯在这儿
Here's Otis!
超女去哪儿了
Where'd Supergirl go?
我不知道  不过我
I don't know but I...
我看见红影闪过了那扇门
I saw a red blur go through that door.
等等
Wait a minute.
D区是男人来的地方  你怎么在这儿
D block's for guys only, what are you doing here?
我...
I, uh...
我是记者
I'm a reporter.
我在餐厅做采访
I was doing an interview in the dining hall
保安把我们赶出去了
when the guards rushed us out.
报道监狱改造  你想发表一下意见吗
The article's on prison reform, maybe you'd care to comment?
我不相信新闻业
I don't trust the press.
他们总是只在出事的时候报道危机
They always parachute into crises like this
却不考虑整个社会体系更大的问题
without any context for the larger systemic issues at play.
太阳
Sun.
什么  什么
What? What?
-不许动  -我只是个记者
- Don't move. - I'm just a reporter.
-真的吗  哪家记者  -凯特科杂志的
- Really, for whom? - For CatCo magazine.
等等  我叫卡拉·丹弗斯
Wait, my name is Kara Danvers.
卡拉·丹弗斯
Kara Danvers?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
她是卡拉·丹弗斯  那个记者
This is Kara Danvers, the journalist.
我给你读的
The one who writes
《纳欣诺市的外星人们》专栏就是她写的
that Aliens of National City column that I read to you.
凯特科其他好文章大多也都是她写的
And most of the other good stuff in CatCo, too.
多谢夸奖
Oh, thanks.
抱歉刚刚拿刀抵着你
Sorry about the shiv.
但是现在这片地方有暴乱
But when a riot breaks out in the block,
谁知道你会碰上什么坏人呢
you never know who you're gonna run into.
我叫史蒂夫·罗麦利
Steve Lomeli.
斯特赖克唯一简报的编辑
Editor of Stryker's one and only newsletter.
不大自由的新闻
The not-so-free press.
很高兴见到新闻界的同行
It's nice to meet another member of the fourth estate.
我很荣幸
Pleasure's mine.
跟我们说说吧  你为什么来斯特赖克
So tell us, what brings you to Stryker's?
当然是私下里来的
Off the record, of course.
我其实...在写有关莱克斯·卢瑟的文章
I'm actually... I'm writing a piece about Lex Luthor.
你不会恰巧知道他的事情吧
You wouldn't happen to know anything about him, would you?
你是今天第二个
You know, you're the second person today
跟我问起那疯子的人了
to ask me about that psycho.
事实就是  我的牢房就在他对面
Truth is, my cell is right across from his.
我可以跟你透露点东西
I could tell you some things.
-当然  都是很深入的信息  -当然
- Deep background, of course. - Of course.
超女  这里是国民警卫队
Supergirl, this is the National Guard.
再不出来我们就进去了
Come out or we're coming in.
任何阻碍我们的人都会被击毙
Anyone in our way will be shot.
简直是疯了  外面还有暴乱
That's crazy. They can't just come in here shooting
他们不能就这么进来乱扫吧
when there's practically a riot going on?
你觉得纳欣诺市的
You think the National
国民警卫队会在意一群罪犯吗
Guard gives a hoot about a bunch of convicts?
我们五秒后开始进攻
We are making our breach in five seconds.
趴到地上去
Lay down flat on the floor...
-快点  我们得趴下  -手放在背后
- Come on, we better get down. -...hands behind your back.
我得走了
Uh, I have to go.
-五  -走? 你疯了吗
- Five... - Go? Are you crazy?
四
Four...
三
Three...
二
Two...
一  上
One. Go!
所有人  趴下
Everybody, down!
上  上  上
Move, move, move.
超女在哪儿
Where is Supergirl?
莉娜
Lena?
我在这儿
I'm here.
这是哪儿
What is this place?
艾美特克
Amertek.
这是超查部的废弃设备
That's the DEO desert facility.
你在计划什么  莱克斯
What are you up to, Lex?
别担心  L先生  一切都在我掌控之下
Don't worry, Mr. L. I got it all under control.
完了
Oh, no.
奥蒂斯
Otis.
没错  我就在你的监狱里
Yes, I am in your cell.
看起来还不错
And it looks great.
站在正中间  当然了
Stand in the middle? Yeah, sure.
我们得马上离开
We've got to get out of here.
不能就这样走  得找到莱克斯
We can't leave all this stuff. We need it to find Lex.
没时间了
There's no time.
你说"这是你应得的"  是什么意思
And by "This is what you get," you mean what?
-尼娅  -布莱尼  我错了
- Nia-- - Brainy, I was wrong.
你不能删除记录
You can't delete the registry.
-我没删  -幸好
- I didn't. - Thank God.
我梦见他们去追杀你了
I had a dream they came for you.
我应该说清楚
I should clarify.
我确实删了名单
I did, in fact, erase the list
超查部服务器里的
from the DEO servers.
但考虑到我们可能会需要它...
But seeing as how there may come a time when we need it...
我下载了一个复件
I downloaded a copy.
在我脑子里
To my brain.
为什么你要这样做  你可能会成为攻击目标
Why would you do that? Now you could be a target.
那就是成为英雄的代价
Well, that's just the cost of being a hero.
布莱尼  那
Oh, Brainy, that's...
那真是很英勇
That's actually very heroic.
你说得对  我应该像你说的那样预见未来
You were right. I should've looked into the future like you'd asked.
在这个问题上  我有了新的想法
I have evolved my views on this topic.
考虑到预见未来的后果
The consequences of seeing the future under consideration,
做正确的事才是当务之急
doing the right thing is an imperative.
再说了  我被捕的几率其实非常低
Besides, the odds of my arrest are actually quite low
考虑到你还不擅长理解你的梦
seeing as how you're not very good at interpreting your dreams.
我想最多只有三分之二的可能
I give it 40/60 at best.
改成二分之三吧
Make that 60/40.
布莱尼
Brainy?
你的总统命令  上校
Your presidential order, Colonel.
这足够了  沃克女士
This will suffice, Miss Walker.
很好很好很好
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
看看这对超女有没有用  很好
See if this won't work on Supergirl. Good.
别害羞  先生们  这是个好东西
Don't be shy, gentlemen. This is the good stuff.
没有我直接命令  任何人不得开枪
Nobody fires without my direct order.
如果她够聪明  她会悄悄地来
And if she's smart, she'll come quietly.
来吧
Okay.
召唤超女
Summon Supergirl.
这要花多长时间
So how long is this supposed to take?
一般不超过一分钟
Normally less than a minute.
但看起来她好像是切断联系了
But it would appear as though she has gone dark.
信号离线
好吧
Okay.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我遵循了你的指示
I followed your orders.
收拾东西
Let's pack it up.
快点  收拾东西  所有东西
Come on, pack it up. All of it.
我们就把这些武器拿走
We'll just be taking the weapons with us.
-你按了两次  -我这样做不是为了你
- You pressed twice. - I didn't do it for you.
我女儿昨晚恐慌症发作了
My daughter had a panic attack last night.
她害怕戒严令和宵禁
She is scared of martial law and the curfew
而且她最喜欢的老师失踪了
and the fact that her favorite teacher has gone missing.
那老师是个外星人
He's an alien.
大概是藏起来了
And presumably in hiding.
但我连这点也不能向她保证  是吧
But I can't promise her that, can I?
是的
No, you can't.
我不喜欢被你操纵
I don't like being manipulated by you
或是那条渴望权力的毒蛇
or that power-hungry snake.
你做得没错
You made the right choice.
我为自己对国家的忠诚而自豪
I prided myself on my loyalty to this country.
我想要什么不重要  这都是为
What I wanted didn't matter, it was about
社会大众谋福祉
serving the greater good.
现在  我在想
Now, I wonder about
那少部分人
the few...
那部分被舍弃的人
the ones left behind.
我女儿会是其中的一员吗
Will my daughter be one of them?
她向我寻求帮助
She is looking to me for help
寻求道德指引
and moral guidance
但如果我自己也参与了这件事
but how can I protect her
那我该如何保护她
if I am party to this?
政府已经确认超女就是
Authorities have identified Supergirl as the attacker
企图释放斯特赖克岛囚犯的袭击者
in an attempt to free prisoners of Stryker's Island.
企图释放囚犯吗
Attempt to free prisoners?
荒唐
That's ridiculous.
看到人们用这些创造性的新方式
It's always a joy to see the new and creative ways
来憎恨好人  就觉得好笑
people find to hate the good guys.
那个囚犯  斯蒂夫  他没错
That prisoner, Steve, he wasn't wrong.
我确实恶化了事态
I did make things worse.
有多少囚犯差点因为我而死
How many prisoners almost died today because of me?
我让你在监狱里面临危险
I put you in jeopardy at the prison.
我让你在超查部里面临危险
And you were in jeopardy at the DEO.
很显然  我现在所做的
It's clear I am doing
利大于弊
more harm than good right now.
所以我认为超女是时候该
So I think it's time Supergirl
保持低调了
lay low.
还有其他办法能得到真相
There are other ways to get to the truth.
詹姆斯  我收到了你的消息
James, I got your message.
听起来很紧急  怎么了
It sounded urgent. What's up?
又发生了
It happened again.
这次我可以看见500英尺远
But this time I could see 500 feet.
感觉就在我眼前
Like it was right in front of me.
我还能听见一些
And I could hear things
常人不该听见的声音
that nobody should be able to hear.
这些可能是幻觉  都是已知的症状
It could be a hallucination. Those are known symptoms.
我也希望如此
I would love to believe that.
真的  但是这次太真实了
I would, but this was too real.
我们必须要告诉莉娜
We have to talk to Lena.
这不只是创伤后应激障碍了
This is more than PTSD.
她摧毁了一个监狱
She destroyed a prison.
她打败了超查部
She outsmarted the DEO.
不知怎地  她知道我们要来
Somehow she knew we were coming.
她似乎总是比我们快一步
She always seems to be one step ahead of us.
如果你想我抓住她  我需要能相信的人
I need people I can trust if you want me to bring her down.
去吧
Go ahead.
授权自由之子
Deputize the Children of Liberty.
是的  你是被引爆了
Yes, you were detonated.
但我们又把你装好了
But we put you back together again.
谢谢你来见我
Thank you for meeting with me.
很荣幸能接受卡拉·丹弗斯的采访
Ah! What an honor to be interviewed by Kara Danvers.
一定要保密  好吗
Just make sure it stays off the record, okay?
绝对严严实实的  我保证
Oh, deep, deep background, I promise.
真可惜莱克斯的秘密监狱实验室
It's a shame Lex's secret prison lab
被奥蒂斯·格雷夫斯摧毁了
was destroyed by that Otis Graves.
但因为我这里没有安全的
But since there's no such thing as a secure Wi-Fi network
无线网络
with me in the building...
莱克斯的硬盘
Lex's hard drive.
那个密室里的电脑上的一切
Everything that was on the computer in that secret room.
谢谢你  斯蒂夫
Thank you, Steve.
你能把他绳之以法我就很感谢了
I'm just grateful you're bringing him to justice.
能有这样的工具我就很感谢了
I'm grateful I have the tools to do it.
追求正义的过程中  最强大的力量
There's nothing more powerful in the pursuit of justice
就是媒体的力量
than the power of the press.
有句老话叫什么
What do they say?
笔头强于剑
The pen is mightier than the sword.
或许比披风还强大
Maybe even mightier than a cape.